<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graduate Life on juppytt&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://juppytt.github.io/categories/graduate-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graduate Life on juppytt&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 20:37:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juppytt.github.io/categories/graduate-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ACM CCS 2024 Reflection</title>
      <link>https://juppytt.github.io/posts/ccs24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 20:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juppytt.github.io/posts/ccs24/</guid>
      <description>This is a personal note for the ACM CCS 2024 I made after the event. CCS 2024 was held in Salt Lake City, Utah, USA. It was my second time attending CCS, but this time I had the privilege of presenting my work.
Pre-Conference Trip The gifts from Zhejiang university students
Before heading to CCS, some phd students from Zhejiang university reached out to me to hang out together when they stop over in Seoul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A review of 2023: Surprises, Triumphs, and Failures</title>
      <link>https://juppytt.github.io/posts/2023-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 22:37:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juppytt.github.io/posts/2023-review/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the end of 2023, and as I look back on the year, I can only say that it was a year full of research. I remember the days spent in front of the computer, reading papers, and conducting experiments. Of course, there were other events this year, including the creation of this blog (yay!). So, I decided it would be nice to write a review of 2023, to reflect on this year and to prepare for the next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Series: Graduate School Productivity - Introduction</title>
      <link>https://juppytt.github.io/posts/series-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juppytt.github.io/posts/series-productivity/</guid>
      <description>Time flies in graduate school! Having spent 3.5 years as a PhD student, one thing I&amp;rsquo;ve learned is that I should be super-efficient in managing my time and energy.
I&amp;rsquo;m not someone you&amp;rsquo;d label as &amp;ldquo;born productive&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m a typical &amp;ldquo;P&amp;rdquo;-type person according to Myers-Briggs Type Indicator (MBTI)&amp;ndash;indicative of a spontaneous and flexible nature. As many P-type people do, I&amp;rsquo;m prone to distraction and have difficulty in sticking to routines. Daily to-do lists or planners are ways to self-torture by confining free will into a fixed schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
