<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on juppytt&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on juppytt&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hugging (Evil) Face: Security issues in Hugging Face</title>
      <link>/posts/hugging-evil-face/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugging-evil-face/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In recent years, emerging technology in Machine Learning and Large Language Model (LLM) had led to the development of ML/LLM-powered applications. One of the popular service for ML/LLM application is Hugging Face. In this post, I would like to describe the potential security risks in current Hugging Face, especially in Spaces.
Hugging Face Hugging Face is a AI community that provides a lot of machine learning models, datasets, and applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security-hardening ARM64 Linux kernel</title>
      <link>/posts/linux-arm64-hardening/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/linux-arm64-hardening/</guid>
      <description>Intro In the first year of my Ph.D, I ambitiously began a research on protecting the Linux kernel against data-only attacks. My research especially focused on protecting security-critical objects and pointers leveraging the ARM&amp;rsquo;s upcoming hardware security features (PAC and MTE).
Building such a kernel hardening system required me to tackle several key issues:
Cross-compiling the kernel (X86 -&amp;gt; ARM64) Cross-module kernel analysis Linux kernel instrumentation Connecting the cross-module analysis with kernel build system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
